<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Info IoT</string>

    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

    <string name="homeDescription">Select one of the following elements to see his information!</string>

    <string name="cables">"Cables are essential components of computer systems, providing the necessary physical connections that enable seamless communication and functionality among various hardware peripherals and components."</string>

    <string name="maleToMale">MALE TO MALE</string>
    <string name="maleToMaleDescription">"A male-to-male cable is a cable that has the same type of connector at both ends, that is, the \'male' connector. These cables are used to connect devices that have the same type of port or connector, thus requiring a direct connection between them without the need for additional adapters or cables.\n\nFor example, a male-to-male Ethernet cable is used to directly connect two network devices, such as two computers or a computer and a router, without the need for a network switch or hub. Similarly, a male-to-male HDMI cable is used to directly connect two HDMI devices, such as a Blu-ray player to a television, without the need for an adapter.\n\nIn summary, male-to-male cables are useful when you need a direct connection between two devices that have the same type of port or connector."</string>

    <string name="maleToFemale">MALE TO FEMALE</string>
    <string name="maleToFemaleDescription">"A male-to-female cable has a male connector at one end and a female connector at the other end. It is used to connect devices that have different types of ports or connectors, enabling connection between them.\n\nFor example, a male-to-female USB cable is used to connect a USB device, such as a printer or a camera, to a USB port on a computer. The male end of the cable is plugged into the USB port on the computer, while the female end is plugged into the USB port on the device.\n\nAnother common example is a male-to-female headphone extension cable, which is used to extend the length of headphones. The male end of the cable is plugged into the headphone jack, while the female end is used to connect the headphones to the audio device, such as a phone or a computer."</string>

    <string name="femaleToFemale">FEMALE TO FEMALE</string>
    <string name="femaleToFemaleDescription">"A female-to-female cable is a cable that has \"female\" connectors on both ends. These cables are used to connect two devices that have ports or connectors of the same type and gender. They are typically used in situations where a direct extension or connection between two male cables is needed, without the need for additional adapters.\n\nFor example, a female-to-female USB cable could be used to connect two male USB cables together to extend the connection distance without the need for an additional adapter or connector. Similarly, a female-to-female audio cable can be used to connect two male audio cables, extending the length of the connection for audio devices.\n\nFemale-to-female cables are useful when a direct connection between two male cables of the same type and gender is needed, without the need for additional adapters."</string>

    <string name="jumper"></string>
    <string name="jumperDescription">"A jumper cable, in the context of electronics and computing, is a short cable used to establish a direct connection between two points, such as pins, terminals, or connectors in a circuit, device, or system. These cables generally have identical connectors at both ends and are used for purposes such as hardware setup, interconnection of components within a system, or to facilitate testing and diagnostics.\n\nFor example, on a breadboard or protoboard, a jumper cable could be used to connect two nearby contact points to establish a temporary electrical connection. In electronics, jumper cables are also used to connect the pins of a microcontroller or integrated circuit to other components in a circuit.\n\nIn summary, jumper cables are versatile and useful tools in electronics and computing, used to establish temporary or permanent connections between specific points in a circuit or system."</string>

    <string name="arduino_uno_name">Arduino Uno</string>
    <string name="arduino_uno_description">Basic development board. Arduino Uno is a development board that features an ATmega328P microcontroller. It is ideal for basic electronics and programming projects.</string>

    <!-- Arduino Mega -->
    <string name="arduino_mega_name">Arduino Mega</string>
    <string name="arduino_mega_description">Development board with more ports and memory. Arduino Mega is a development board with an ATmega2560 microcontroller. It offers more ports and memory than Arduino Uno, making it suitable for more complex projects.</string>

    <!-- Arduino Nano -->
    <string name="arduino_nano_name">Arduino Nano</string>
    <string name="arduino_nano_description">Small board with reduced size. Arduino Nano is a compact version of Arduino Uno. It has the same ATmega328P microcontroller but in a smaller form factor, making it ideal for projects with limited space.</string>

    <!-- Arduino Leonardo -->
    <string name="arduino_leonardo_name">Arduino Leonardo</string>
    <string name="arduino_leonardo_description">Board with ATmega32u4 chip and native USB. Arduino Leonardo is a development board that uses the ATmega32u4 microcontroller. It stands out for having native USB support, simplifying communication with the computer and other devices.</string>

    <!-- Arduino Due -->
    <string name="arduino_due_name">Arduino Due</string>
    <string name="arduino_due_description">Board with 32-bit ARM processor. Arduino Due is a development board that uses a 32-bit ARM Cortex-M3 microcontroller. It offers superior performance and is ideal for applications that require more processing power.</string>

    <!-- Arduino Pro Mini -->
    <string name="arduino_pro_mini_name">Arduino Pro Mini</string>
    <string name="arduino_pro_mini_description">Compact board designed for permanent projects. Arduino Pro Mini is a compact version of Arduino Uno. It is designed for permanent projects where size is critical and an integrated USB port is not needed.</string>

    <!-- Arduino Pro Micro -->
    <string name="arduino_pro_micro_name">Arduino Pro Micro</string>
    <string name="arduino_pro_micro_description">Compact board with ATmega32u4 chip. Arduino Pro Micro is similar to Arduino Leonardo but in a smaller form factor. It uses the same ATmega32u4 microcontroller and offers native USB for easy programming and communication.</string>

    <!-- Arduino MKR1000 -->
    <string name="arduino_mkr1000_name">Arduino MKR1000</string>
    <string name="arduino_mkr1000_description">Board with WiFi connectivity. Arduino MKR1000 is a development board that offers integrated WiFi connectivity. It is ideal for IoT projects that require wireless internet connection.</string>

    <!-- Arduino MKR Zero -->
    <string name="arduino_mkr_zero_name">Arduino MKR Zero</string>
    <string name="arduino_mkr_zero_description">Board with 32-bit SAMD21 processor. Arduino MKR Zero uses a 32-bit SAMD21 microcontroller. It offers powerful and energy-efficient performance, making it ideal for applications that require low power consumption.</string>

    <!-- Arduino MKR FOX 1200 -->
    <string name="arduino_mkr_fox_1200_name">Arduino MKR FOX 1200</string>
    <string name="arduino_mkr_fox_1200_description">Board with Sigfox connectivity. Arduino MKR FOX 1200 is a development board that offers integrated Sigfox connectivity. It is ideal for IoT projects that require long battery life and long-range connection.</string>

    <!-- Arduino MKR WAN 1300 -->
    <string name="arduino_mkr_wan_1300_name">Arduino MKR WAN 1300</string>
    <string name="arduino_mkr_wan_1300_description">Board with LoRa connectivity. Arduino MKR WAN 1300 is a development board that offers integrated LoRa connectivity. It is ideal for IoT projects that require long-range connection and low power consumption.</string>

    <!-- Arduino MKR GSM 1400 -->
    <string name="arduino_mkr_gsm_1400_name">Arduino MKR GSM 1400</string>
    <string name="arduino_mkr_gsm_1400_description">Board with GSM connectivity. Arduino MKR GSM 1400 is a development board that offers integrated GSM connectivity. It is ideal for IoT projects that require cellular communication to send and receive data.</string>

    <!-- Arduino MKR NB 1500 -->
    <string name="arduino_mkr_nb_1500_name">Arduino MKR NB 1500</string>
    <string name="arduino_mkr_nb_1500_description">Board with NB-IoT connectivity. Arduino MKR NB 1500 is a development board that offers integrated NB-IoT connectivity. It is ideal for IoT projects that require low power consumption and long-range connection.</string>

    <!-- Arduino MKR VIDOR 4000 -->
    <string name="arduino_mkr_vidor_4000_name">Arduino MKR VIDOR 4000</string>
    <string name="arduino_mkr_vidor_4000_description">Board with integrated FPGA. Arduino MKR VIDOR 4000 is a development board that includes an integrated FPGA. This allows for greater flexibility and processing capability for advanced projects.</string>

    <!-- Arduino Nano 33 IoT -->
    <string name="arduino_nano_33_iot_name">Arduino Nano 33 IoT</string>
    <string name="arduino_nano_33_iot_description">Board with WiFi and Bluetooth connectivity. Arduino Nano 33 IoT is a development board that offers integrated WiFi and Bluetooth connectivity. It is ideal for IoT projects that require wireless communication and low power consumption.</string>

    <!-- Arduino Nano 33 BLE -->
    <string name="arduino_nano_33_ble_name">Arduino Nano 33 BLE</string>
    <string name="arduino_nano_33_ble_description">Board with low-energy Bluetooth connectivity. Arduino Nano 33 BLE is a development board that offers integrated low-energy Bluetooth connectivity. It is ideal for projects that require low-energy wireless communication.</string>

    <!-- Arduino Nano 33 BLE Sense -->
    <string name="arduino_nano_33_ble_sense_name">Arduino Nano 33 BLE Sense</string>
    <string name="arduino_nano_33_ble_sense_description">Board with integrated sensors. Arduino Nano 33 BLE Sense is a development board that includes integrated sensors such as accelerometer, gyroscope, temperature, humidity, and pressure. It is ideal for projects that require motion and environmental detection.</string>

    <!-- Arduino Nano Every -->
    <string name="arduino_nano_every_name">Arduino Nano Every</string>
    <string name="arduino_nano_every_description">Updated version of Arduino Nano. Arduino Nano Every is an updated version of Arduino Nano with an ATmega4809 microcontroller. It offers improved performance and is compatible with existing Arduino Nano libraries and projects.</string>

    <!-- Arduino Nano RP2040 Connect -->
    <string name="arduino_nano_rp2040_connect_name">Arduino Nano RP2040 Connect</string>
    <string name="arduino_nano_rp2040_connect_description">Board based on the RP2040 chip from Raspberry Pi. Arduino Nano RP2040 Connect is a development board that uses the RP2040 chip from Raspberry Pi. It offers powerful performance and is ideal for projects that require advanced processing capability.</string>

</resources>